The Governor has arrived!
- Governor!
My lord, what brings you here?
What are you doing here?
Someone is impersonating the Godfather.
What?!
Someone dares impersonate the Godfather?
Arrest him immediately!
Yes!
Wait!
Which one is
Mr. Carter?
Governor, there are several Carters here.
Which one do you mean?
The groom holding the wedding here today.
That would be me.
This is my wedding with Lady Livia.
The Governor of Emeraldstone greets Mr. Carter.
Please accept it,
Mr. Carter.
Thank you, Governor.
You’re too kind.
It’s only proper.
See that?
Even the Governor came personally to my wedding.
What do you have to compete with me?
Darling, now do you see I was the right choice?
I never doubted my choice for a second.
Stop looking at me like that.
You might regret it.
Hah…
you should worry about yourself.
Impersonating the Godfather?
You’re going to hang for that.
It isn’t a crime that ends with mere death.
Do you think I’m a fake?
This man is also a
Mr. Carter?
Governor, that’s my worthless older brother,
a disowned son of House Carter,
nothing but a miner.
Then he truly is worthless.
Los!
How can you be so blind that
you fail to recognize the Godfather?
What?!
You’re saying I failed to recognize the Godfather?
This is the man you should be congratulating.
Lord Severin, the Godfather of the Sovereign Sanctum.